Yes, yes, yes, fear is gone, no more fears,
laughter comes, tears disappear, free to
life without fear, determine
our goals, welcome, we got passion, morning morning
morning in digital technology, we got
passion, morning morning morning, we keep
innovating, I run with
enthusiasm to make dreams come true, as we
celebrate,
Liv
C are are are for long, Run as long as there is still time,
ye, As long as there is still energy, the
path of life has many directions, happy if there is someone to
guard, we got passion, morning morning morning
in digital technology,
passion, morning morning morning, we keep
innovating, don't
[Music]
give up because life is a
gift, celebrate life with
hope, we are FW we
are I
dare, I run with
enthusiasm to make dreams come true, as we
celebrate,
Liv celeb are are are
for the
[Music]
R FW